https://www.reliantsafe.com/privacy

Solutions
Security Operations Center (SOC)
Investigation Response Team (IRT)
Law Enforcement Liaison
Virtual Building Management Assistant (VBMA)
Solutions+-
Security Operations Center (SOC)
Investigation Response Team (IRT)
Law Enforcement Liaison
Virtual Building Management Assistant (VBMA)
TERMS & CONDITIONS
This website and the materials within it are property of RELIANT SAFETY, LLC. The following basic terms govern the use of the website. By using the RELIANT SAFETY website, you agree to follow and be bound by the terms and conditions contained herein. These terms may be changed from time to time, and your use of the website following these changes will confirm your agreement to abide and be bound by the terms as modified from time to time.
This website is operated by RELIANT SAFETY. Throughout this website, RELIANT SAFETY can be referred to as “We”, “Our”, “Us”. We offer this website, including all the information, tools, and services available through this website, to the user, conditioned upon the user’s acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies, and notices mentioned herein, which acceptance is confirmed by use of this website.
CONTENTS
All contents of the RELIANT SAFETY website, including product images, trademarks, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, artwork, images and any video and/or audio material are copyrights, trademarks and other intellectual property owned and controlled exclusively by RELIANT SAFETY, LLC and its subsidiaries and affiliates (“RELIANT SAFETY”).
You may not copy, reproduce, publish, transmit, or otherwise use copyrighted or trademarked documents on this website without prior written consent. This includes the use of RELIANT SAFETY trademarks for tags, hidden text, or otherwise using the trademarks to get a higher ranking on search engines. RELIANT SAFETY retains all rights in its copyrights and trademarks, trade names, brand names, and trade dress represented on this website. RELIANT SAFETY will aggressively enforce all intellectual property rights applicable to the content.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Links may be included on the website of RELIANT SAFETY to websites owned by third parties. RELIANT SAFETY does not control third-party websites and is not responsible for any damage you may incur using these third-party websites. Creating a link to the RELIANT SAFETY website is prohibited without the prior written consent of RELIANT SAFETY.
YOUR SUBMISSION
Any communication or material that you transmit to the website by e-mail or otherwise, including data, questions, comments, suggestions or other, is and will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary, unless otherwise indicated in our privacy policy. Anything you transmit or post may be used by the company or its subsidiaries for any purpose, including, but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, dissemination, and display. Also, we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in any communication you send to the website for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, the development, manufacture, and marketing of products using this information.
INDEMNIFICATION
You agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless RELIANT SAFETY, its shareholders, members, partners, officers, directors, employees, agents, distributors, vendors and affiliates of and against any claim, demands, liability, cost or expense of a third party, including without limitation reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from your violation of any of these conditions, including, but not limited to, allegations, damages or claims relating to any of your messages or communications in forums or facilities on the website, or for infringements or violation of third-party rights.
DISCLAIMER AND WARRANTY
RELIANT SAFETY provides this website, its content, and all associated services on an “as is” and “as available” basis. RELIANT SAFETY makes no representations or warranties of any kind whatsoever, express or implied, as to the operation of this website, the information, content, materials or products included on this website, or the functionality of all associated services. To the fullest extent permitted by law, RELIANT SAFETY disclaims any implied warranties, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of title, merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, effort, rules, adequacy, the availability, accuracy, reliability, completeness or timeliness of the content, or non-infringement, as well as warranties arising from the use of the website. Also, RELIANT SAFETY makes no representations or warranties that this website and its contents are accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free, or that any disclosure on this website satisfies government regulations regarding disclosure information about certain products. RELIANT SAFETY is not responsible for typographical errors or omissions relating to pricing, text, photography or any other content on this website.
By using the RELIANT SAFETY website, you acknowledge that your use of the website, including your use of any related content, data or software distributed by, downloaded or accessed from or through this website, and all associated services are only at your own risk. RELIANT SAFETY does not warrant or guarantee that its website, servers or e-mails sent by or on behalf of RELIANT SAFETY are free of viruses, worms, cookies or other harmful components. Also, RELIANT SAFETY does not guarantee the continuous, uninterrupted and error-free operation of its website, or that all communications between you and RELIANT SAFETY, or between you and any other user of the website, will be secured access or free of third-party interference.
RELIANT SAFETY will not be liable for damages of any kind arising out of or otherwise related to your use or inability to use this website or associated services, including, but not limited to, direct, indirect, incidental, punitive and consequential, even if RELIANT SAFETY was advised or should have known of the possibility of such damages. Without limiting the foregoing, RELIANT SAFETY will not be liable for damage to your computer, telecommunication equipment, or other property caused by or arising out of your access or use of this website, or your downloading of any materials from this website, or for any damages resulting from unauthorized access by a third party and the use of your personal information stored on computers and/or servers of RELIANT SAFETY.
REVISIONS AND UPDATES
RELIANT SAFETY may occasionally make revisions to its website and reserves the right to do so without recourse to any user.
FEEDBACK
Any comments or feedback submitted by the users of the website must be and remain the property of RELIANT SAFETY, and we are not required to pay or respond to these comments or feedback provided by users.
GOVERNING LAW
The laws of the United States of America shall govern these terms of use without regard to any provision of conflict of law. Any dispute arising out of these terms of use shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of any state or federal court located in the United States of America.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Questions about the terms and conditions should be sent to us at
Contact Email Address: info@reliantsafe.com
Company Mailing Address:
Reliant Safety
909 3rd Avenue, 21st Floor
New York, NY 10022
PRIVACY POLICY
We appreciate your interest in RELIANT SAFETY, LLC (“RELIANT SAFETY”, “we” or “us”), as well as all platforms and other website and content materials (the “Website and Content Materials”) provided by us and upon which there is a direct link to this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”).
This website is the sole property of RELIANT SAFETY, LLC. RELIANT SAFETY respects the privacy of all persons using our Website and Content Materials, so we will do everything reasonably practicable to safeguard the privacy of our users. Our website is not designed for use by persons under the age of 18.
By accessing or/and using our website, you agree to abide by all the terms of this Privacy Policy, and you also agree to the collection, use, and sharing (when necessary) of your data and information as outlined in this Policy. Refrain from using our website if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy.
The term ‘non-personal information’ refers to data that we sometimes collect from you that has no direct connection with your identity. It will also refer to aggregate data that we use for Website and Content Materials improvement or other functions on our website, as stated in this Privacy Policy.
EXTERNAL LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES OR SERVICES
This website may contain links or ads to other services, websites or advertisements. Please note, if you choose to visit any ads, services, or websites, by or from a banner, link or another type of promotional material on our website that leads to a third-party’s website or services, then such link, website, banner advertisement, or service does not represent an authorization or endorsement by us of, or an affiliation with, such third-party, or constitute an approval of their privacy policies or information security policies or practices. RELIANT SAFETY does not have control over third-party websites or services. Every service or website follows different policies regarding the use and disclosure of the personal and non-personal information submitted to them. We strongly advise that you always carefully review the privacy policies or statements of the other websites or links you visit from our website, as RELIANT SAFETY will not be liable or responsible for any loss or damage caused by linked websites or services.
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
Except as provided herein, we will not distribute, lease or sell your personal information to any third party unless we are compelled by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send promotional information about relevant third parties if you notify us that you so desire.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
Personal Information
We collect personal information you choose to provide to us, which may include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, etc.
Location Information
Depending on the settings and permissions on your device, we may collect exact or approximate information about your location as determined through data such as GPS, IP address, etc.
Users may use the RELIANT SAFETY Website and Content Materials without granting permission to collect their location information, but this may limit our service offerings to you.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We also collect information related to how you use our website, your preferences, and regular settings. We sometimes get this information through the use of cookies, pixel tags, and similar methods of identifying and tracking unique identifiers. You have the choice to opt out of standard cookies via settings on your browser. If you have questions on this or regarding your choices about how we share your information, please send us an email.
Device Information
The website may detect what type of devices you use to access the service; such as the device model, operating systems and versions, serial numbers, file names, their locations and versions, your preferred languages, advertising identifiers, mobile service providers, and mobile network information.
Usage Log Information
When you use our website, we keep logs from your server; this may include your IP address, date and time of usage, specific service used, and other relevant activity, type and version of browser used, and sometimes third-party services used before using our service.
HOW WE UTILIZE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
We analyze information gathered, and use the results to improve the delivery and content of the services offered to you on our website, to personalize our Website and Content Materials or to provide products that properly fit each’s user experience, services, and programs. We may also use this data when aggregated to offer services or to understand the general usage of our website, programs, or corresponding services.
We may share your information with a third party when necessary. For instance;
When we confirm beyond reasonable doubt that sharing such information is required to track, reach or carry out legal proceedings against a person infringing on or violating RELIANT SAFETY’s property rights, or the rights of another party that could be affected by such occurrences, or to fulfill governmental and quasi-governmental demands, court injunctions or anything of this nature.
We might share your information with our affiliates, vendors or service providers to carry out certain activities on our behalf (e.g., analyzing information, marketing, offering services to users, process transactions, etc.).
We might share the information to facilitate a process on your behalf.
If we share the information as part of a transaction, transfer or sale of all or part of our assets (e.g., if our company happens to be acquired by another entity, user information may be part of the acquired assets).
As explicitly outlined in this Privacy Policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTED
Except as provided herein, we do not share website users’ personal information with any third parties. We may make use of Internet analysis tools, like Google Analytics, to analyze how you use our Website and Content Materials. We use such information to offer advertisements that correspond to your interests and preferences. We may also share non-personal information with our business partners, affiliates or clients to help improve the services they offer.
DATA SECURITY
While making our Website and Content Materials available to you, we have put in place required physical and electronic securities, and measures to safeguard your information and help prevent unauthorized access to your data. We endeavor to ensure only proper and legal use of the information we collect from our users.
Also, we try to limit employees’ access to users’ personal information even when carrying out their normal duties. We review our security measures periodically to include new technology and up-to-date strategies.
MODIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy is an important part of our Terms and Conditions, which you agree to by using our website and all associated services. You agree that RELIANT SAFETY may modify this Privacy Policy and also our Terms and Conditions at any time without notice or your consent.
This website uses cookies and other analytical tools to ensure you have the best experience on our site. By continuing to browse on our website, you agree to our use of cookies. To learn more, please read our Privacy Policy.I Accept
Products
Video Surveillance
Roof Alarms
Intercoms
Access Control
Employee Tracking
Solutions
Security Operations Center (SOC)
Investigation Response Team (IRT)
Law Enforcement Liaison
Virtual Building Management Assistant (VBMA)
System Design
Illegal Sublet Detection
Results
Expertise
Company
Leadership
Careers
Security Hotline 1-844-735-4723
Get In Touch
© 2020 Reliant Safety, LLC. All rights reserved. Reliant Safety reserves the right to change product offerings without prior announcement.
Privacy|Contact
link
Contact Us
T: (844) 735-4723
F: (212) 758-8090
Our Passion, Your Security
Founded in 2009, Reliant Safety provides comprehensive building management and security solutions for the multi-family housing market, educational facilities, office buildings, and all other real estate sectors. Building owners and managers rely on Reliant Safety to assess threats and monitor surveillance for situational awareness and effective management of over 20,000 residential units nationwide.
Security Hotline 1-844-735-4723|Contact|Careers
Tell us a little about yourself, and we’ll be in touch right away.
Please complete all fields.
Product Interest (select all that apply)Video SurveillanceRoof AlarmsIntercomsAccess ControlEmployee TrackingSecurity Operations CenterField Investigation TeamLaw Enforcement LiaisonBuilding Management SupportSystem DesignIllegal Sublet Detection
Please leave this field empty.
